statementlook.com 2002-04-11

# Statementlook - Online Privacy Statement

Effective Date: November 23, 2001

Thank you for visiting the Statementlook web site, operated by First Data Resources Inc. (FDR) in cooperation with the credit card issuers FDR serves. Protecting your privacy is very important to us. Our Online Privacy Statement is designed to inform you about our online collection and use of personal information. This Online Privacy Statement reflects the policies covering personal information collected by us on this web site, on or after the effective date shown above.

Collection and Use of Information  
Except as otherwise provided below, the only personal information we collect about you online is information you voluntarily provide us. We collect and use the information you provide to us online only as necessary to verify your identity and provide you with the information or services you have requested.

In addition to the information you provide to us, our web site software may collect information about your browser type in order to assist you in accessing and viewing your information on our web site, and we may collect information about the number of times you access information on our web site for administrative purposes.

Disclosure of Information  
It is our policy to treat your account information as confidential. We will disclose information to third parties about your account or the transactions you make ONLY:  

  * as necessary to complete a transaction you have authorized; 
  * as requested by your credit card issuer; or 
  * as necessary to comply with a government agency or court order. 

Security  
At Statementlook, security is a priority. We take every precaution, including the use of advanced technology, to protect personal information collected online against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. The information you provide to us on our web site is encrypted and protected with an encryption method called Secure Socket Layer (SSL). While on a secure page, the padlock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked or open when you are just 'surfing'. We continually review and enhance our security systems to protect your information and ensure the integrity of that information.

Links  
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage you to be careful when leaving our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. When you access your account information on our site, you may also find information concerning the privacy policies and practices of your credit card issuer. Those policies and practices are specific to your card issuer and are also separate and distinct from the privacy policies and practices of Statementlook. This Online Privacy Statement applies only to information collected by this web site.

Cookies  
This web site uses one cookie to maintain the session ID. This cookie is used to identify your browser to Statementlook.
